<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
​  <id>org.frescobaldi.Frescobaldi</id>
​  <metadata_license>CC0</metadata_license>
​  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
​  <name>Frescobaldi</name>
​  <summary>LilyPond Music Editor</summary>
​
​  <description>
​    <p>
​      Frescobaldi is an advanced text editor to edit LilyPond sheet music files.
      It aims to be powerful, yet lightweight and easy to use.
​    </p>
​    <p>Features:</p>
​    <ul>
​      <li>Powerful text editor with syntax highlighting and automatic completion</li>
​      <li>Music view with advanced Point &amp; Click</li>
      <li>Midi player to proof-listen LilyPond-generated MIDI files</li>
      <li>Midi capturing to enter music</li>
      <li>Powerful Score Wizard to quickly setup a music score</li>
      <li>Snippet Manager to store and apply text snippets, templates or scripts</li>
      <li>Use multiple versions of LilyPond, automatically selects the correct version</li>
      <li>Built-in LilyPond documentation browser and built-in User Guide</li>
      <li>Smart layout-control functions like coloring specific objects in the PDF</li>
      <li>MusicXML, Midi and ABC import</li>
      <li>Modern user interface with configurable colors, fonts and keyboard shortcuts</li>
      <li>Translated into the following languages: Dutch, English, French, German, Italian, Czech, Russian, Spanish, Galician, Turkish, Polish, Brazillian Portugese and Ukrainian.</li>
​    </ul>
​    <p>
​      Frescobaldi is designed to run on all major operating systems (Linux, Mac OS X
      and MS Windows). It is named after Girolamo Frescobaldi (1583-1643), an Italian
      composer of keyboard music in the late Renaissance and early Baroque period.
​    </p>
​  </description>
​
​  <screenshots>
​    <screenshot type="default">
​      <caption>Main editor view with PDF preview</caption>
​      <image>http://frescobaldi.org/images/frescobaldi1-en.png</image>
​    </screenshot>
​    <screenshot>
      <caption>Magnifier glass</caption>
​      <image>http://frescobaldi.org/images/magnifier1-small-en.png</image>
​    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Snippet manager and editor</caption>
      <image>http://frescobaldi.org/images/snippet2-small-en.png</image>
    </screenshot>
​  </screenshots>
​
​  <url type="homepage">http://frescobaldi.org/</url>
​
​</component>
